// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How long does it the sun’s rays take to reach Earth?",
    answer: "8 minutes",
    options: [
      "8 minutes",
      "5 minutes",
      "2 minutes",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is a human-made object stuck orbiting Earth called?",
    answer: "Space junk",
    options: [
      "It can be anything",
      "Dark matter",
      "Space junk",
      "Drogue"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Name the spacecraft that carried the first astronauts to the moon?",
    answer: "Apollo 11",
    options: [
      "International Space Station",
      "Vostok",
      "Tiangong Space Station",
      "Apollo 11"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How long does it take the moon to pass through all its phases?",
    answer: "29 days",
    options: [
      "18 hours",
      "29 days",
      "A year",
      "21 days"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who described Saturn’s rings as the 'ears of a teacup'?",
    answer: "Galileo",
    options: [
      "Archimedes",
      "Galileo",
      "Ramanujan",
      "Claudius Ptolemy"
    ]
  },
  
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which star is the Alpha Ursa Minoris?",
     answer: "Polaris",
    options: [
       "Canis Major",
       "Alpha Centauri",
       "Andromeda",
       "Polaris"
     ]
   },
   
   {
      numb: 7,
     question: "What do scientists call the disk that encircles a back hole?",
     answer: "Accretion Disk",
    options: [
       "Galactic bulge",
       "Accretion Disk",
       "Kosmolyot",
       "L-band"
     ]
   },
   { numb: 8,
     question: "How long does it take the moon to orbit the Earth?",
     answer: "28 days",
    options: [
       "28 days",
       "12 days",
       "a year",
       "few days"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 9,
     question: "What do you call a large group of stars, dust, and gas?",
     answer: "Galaxy",
    options: [
       "Meteor",
       "A star",
       "Black hole",
       "Galaxy"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 10,
     question: "Which astronaut is famous for having written his daughter’s initials on the moon?",
     answer: "Gene Cernan",
    options: [
       "Isaac Newton",
       "Christiaan Huygens",
       "Gene Cernan",
       "Giovanni Cassini"
     ]
   },
];